



KLITI HAMATAJ

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

ABOUT

Since I graduated in Geoinformatics Engineering I was always interested in technology and communication. For the last 3 years, I have worked in an environment where teamwork was critical and product quality and delivery was essential. Decided to become a developer to push even more my problemsolving, creative and strategic thinking skills. I'm a fast learner and flexible with technologies and stack. Focused on ensuring absolute customer satisfaction through delivery of exceptional customer services. Eager to find a position in the tech industry where I could bring all my skills together to continue improving and learning as a Full-Stack Developer.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Ruby, Ruby on Rails
- APIs, JSON, scraping
- HTML5, CSS/SCSS, Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Relational databases, SQL, PostgreSQL
- Wireframes, prototyping, UI design
- Test-driven development
- MVC Architecture
- Git, GitHub, technical workflow
- Heroku
- GIS Mapping Software
- Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

LE WAGON FULL-STACK CODING BOOTCAMP

| Brussels | Batch #462 | September 2020 - February 2021

POLYTECHNIC UNIVERSITY OF TIRANA

Bachelor Degree in "Geoinformatics Engineering" 2011 - 2015

LANGUAGES

- Albanian: Native proficiency
- English: Full professional proficiency
- Italian Full professional proficiency
- French: Limited working proficiency

CONTACT



+32 465 22 88 95



hamatajkliti@gmail.com



<u>github.com/KlitiHamataj</u>



in linkedin.com/in/hamataj

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

ARTSOUILLE

Co-created a Web-App to foster artistic collaboration and allow artists to meet and create art together. Built with Ruby on Rails, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, GitHub and deployed on Heroku

RENTaPLANET

Co-created a copy of Airbnb but instead of renting apartments, you can rent your own planet. Built with Ruby on Rails, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, GitHub and deployed on Heroku.

EXPERIENCE

LE WAGON FULL-STACK CODING BOOTCAMP

| Brussels | Batch #462 | September 2020 - February 2021

Intensive coding bootcamp learning HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, OOP, MVC architecture, JQuery, AJAX, SQL, Git, GitHub, Heroku and Ruby on Rails

COMMIS DE CUISINE, PASTA MAKER

Atelier des Pates 2017 to Present

- Production of fresh pasta
- Ensured good nutritional standards are maintained when preparing meals
- Properly used and maintained all kitchen equipment
- Performed duties in a fast paced environment

BAR MANAGER

Self-Employed 2016 to 2017

- Scheduled, interviewed, trained new staff
- Addressed complaints and resolved problems with both staff and customers
- Established new marketing techniques increasing overall revenue

PHOTOGRAPHER

Studio "Kejsi" 2015 to 2016

- Photographed portraits and commercial subjects according to client specification
- Graphics editing with Adobe Photoshop
- Helped in the conceptualization of social media advertisements

SALES MANAGER

Dorolat shpk" 2014 to 2015

- Developed growth strategies and plans
- Handled many details, projects and personalities using professional and courteous skills
- Built lasting business relationships through performance and credibility.
- Developed positive rapport with people at all levels of responsibility